gtaa.com 2013-12-07

# Privacy Policy

The GTAA is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals using the GTAA’s websites: torontopearson.com, festi.ca, and apps.torontopearson.com, in addition to other domain names which automatically redirect to torontopearson.com or festi.ca (the “Website(s)”). We will maintain personal information collected through the Website(s) in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We do not sell, share, or rent personal information collected from you to others in any way that is not mentioned in our Privacy Policy. The GTAA is the sole owner of all personal information collected on the Website(s).  
The GTAA will use personal information collected to perform statistical analysis of user behaviour based on the Website(s) log files. This includes site usage patterns gathered during thousands of user visits to the Website(s) each month but does not contain identifying information about any individual.  

## Obtaining your Consent

By using the Website(s), you give the GTAA permission to collect, use and disclose (to third parties under contract to the GTAA to provide certain services to the public) personal information about you including information that is collected by cookies. The information you provide helps us to see how the Website(s) is used in order to provide relevant content and make changes to our existing content to better serve you. In cases where you give personal information for a service performed by a third party under contract to the GTAA, the information provided will be received directly by such third party solely for the purpose of providing the particular service to you. Such services include, for example, the Airport Customer Assistance Program (ACAP) for persons requiring mobility assistance.  
The GTAA has a Privacy Policy concerning the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. View the complete [Privacy Policy](http://torontopearson.com/en/Complete_Privacy_Policy/ "Complete Privacy Policy")[](http://torontopearson.com/en/Complete_Privacy_Policy/ "Privacy Policy").

The GTAA may occasionally amend its Privacy Policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and periodically check to see if changes have been made.

## Questions?

If you wish to change any personal information you have given us, or have any questions about the website, you can contact us via email at [webmaster@gtaa.com](mailto:mailto:webmaster@gtaa.com).
